fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
Ugh... what are you here for now?
It's our reunion after so long,
and you're awfully cold.
Don't tell me that you came to
assassinate Hokage-sama?
No, no...
I don't have enough
subordinates for that yet...
I've heard of the excellence ones
of this village
and thought I'd put dibs on them.
A little while ago, I gave that
same Curse Mark as a present.
There's a kid that I want.
Selfish as always.
That kid will die.
Certainly...
The odds are 1 in 10
that he'll survive,
but he may survive just like you did.
This kid, you really like him, huh?
Are you jealous?
Are you still holding a grudge that
I used you and threw you away?
Unlike you, that kid will excel...
For one thing, he inherited
the Uchiha ability.
He has beautiful features
and is a vessel who
can become my heir.
If that kid lived,
it makes things interesting.
Be sure not to cancel this test.
Three from my village are also
under your care...
Make me enjoy it.
If something happens
to deprive me of my fun,
consider it the end of Leaf Village.
We've secured food and water
after spending half a day.
And now most teams have halted activity.
As we planned,
this is the time that we attack.
We'll split up into three
and go scouting.
However, whether we find
other teams or not,
we return to this place.
Got it?
— Okay.
— Roger.
Okay. Scatter!
Super Eyebrow Platonic!
I Will Protect You
to the Death!!
I can't fall asleep...
I need to protect these two.
I slept great!
Naruto!
Sasuke-kun!
Did you take care of us?
Thank you, Sakura-chan!
We're totally better because of you!
That's good...
A prey must always stay tense
and flee desperately
in front of the predator!
My voice is gone!
It was just a dream...
Is it daybreak already?!
No, no way!
A squirrel?
Don't surprise me like that!
Oh!
That was too close.
Do you think she noticed?
The Paper Bomb we put on the squirrel...
No, that's not it.
Huh? Then what? What was it?
We'll probably find out if we go closer.
So... we should get going now.
If I can catch all twenty of these leaves
before they hit the ground
Sakura-san will start to like me.
If... if I can't catch
even one of the leaves...!
It'll be an unanswered love forever.
Or rather...
You're too Bushy!
That's what she'll say.
One, two, three, four...
five, six, seven, eight...
nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen,
nine...!
Ugh, nineteen...
One more!
That's...!
Phew... just in time.
This is called a Paper Bomb
and it explodes after some time.
Who did such an awful thing?
Stop hiding and come out.
Crap! We scrambled to hide, you know?!
Man, he's a damn pain
and we've been discovered!
Strategy One, "hide and let it pass,"
was a failure!
So now we carry out Strategy Two!
Huh? Are you serious?
What? You have a problem with that?
There's no question of success.
Well, I guess it's all right but...
Wow! To meet last year's Number One
rookie, Hyuga Neji-sama, in a place like this!
C-Can I have your autograph?
So it's just you guys?
Take that! Strategy Two, "head over heals
infatuation with my sex appeal"!
I'd been wanting to meet you
for some time, you know?
Get lost!
Why? Why doesn't my sexiness work?!
Crap, it ticks me off, damn!
Did you just raise your fists to me,
and does that mean you want to fight?
N-No...
Of course not.
Then get lost.
Stealing a scroll from cowardly wimps
like you
would only make me
the laughing stock of the village.
Y-Yes!
Huh... Really just like cockroaches.
Just as I thought.
A fellow like that wouldn't take
a scroll away from wimps like us
unless we were to turn on him.
All right! Let's go find some wimps!
Like I've been saying
there's no one wimpier than us...
So a no-sleep lookout?
But it's not necessary anymore.
Wake Sasuke-kun up.
We want to battle with him.
Y-You bastards...
What're you saying?
What is it you're after?
I know the one called Orochimaru
is calling the shots from the shadows!
Huh?!
What's that strange bruise on
the back of Sasuke-kun's neck?
You did this to Sasuke-kun.
How can you say you want to fight him?!
I wonder... what he has on his mind?
However, I can't stay quiet
after hearing that.
I will kill this girl,
I'll also kill this Sasuke character.
Wait, Zaku.
Huh? What is it?
It's so cliché.
It's the color of dirt
that's just been dug up.
This grass, it doesn't grow in
a place like this, does it?
Damn!
You know, with a trap...
there's no point unless you
make it so it's not discovered.
Huh, how ridiculous!
So that Kunai knife was so the squirrel
wouldn't be caught in the trap?
We kill her now!
A log?!
A trap above too? Watch out!
Just kidding.
What?!
Clearly you have no talent.
Someone like you needs to
make more of an effort or else!
Leaf Hurricanes!
What?! This guy...
Then you also should... make an effort!
Who are you?
I'm the beautiful green beast
of Leaf Village, Rock Lee!
Why are you here?
I will always appear...
whenever you're in trouble!
Or should I say...
It was really because of you,
now run along.
But right now, I'm also
your enemy!
I did say this once before, didn't I?
That I'll protect you until I die.
Please go out with me!
I'll protect you until I die!
Oh...
T-Thanks.
Yes!
Perfect! I did it!
Guy-sensei, that was perfect!
I guess it can't be helped...
Zaku. I'll give you Sasuke-kun.
I will kill them!
As far as I can tell,
Sakura-san is in no condition to fight.
That Bushy-Brow guy is
pretty proficient with Taijutsu...
Looks like I can have some fun!
There is a trick to your attack, isn't there?
I won't just simply avoid it.
You showed me your Jutsu before.
This guy... he's strong.
Having said that,
the odds aren't good since
it's one versus three.
I'm gonna have to take a chance.
One person at a time...
I'll give it my all and take each down!
There's no one at all that seems wimpy!
Well, the only team that's weaker
than us is the Naruto team.
Idiot! You know what you're saying?
What?!
No question Naruto and Sakura are lame!
But that team has
the super genius Sasuke-kun!
Hah! I wonder...
In actual battle that genius
might easily be beaten.
What?!
All right, all right,
I apologize for irritating you.
What a pain...
I say one negative thing about
Sasuke and I get the evil eye, every time...
There's no way Sasuke-kun
could be taken down!
Sakura's a different matter though!
Huh?!
Hey! Sasuke has collapsed...
...and Sakura is fighting.
What did you say?
Hey!
He's late.
That Lee...
Something's not right.
He's always precise about time.
Perhaps he ran into the enemy...
Could it be...?
Huh, that wouldn't have happened.
In any case, let's find Lee!
Right!
Yes! I've finally mastered it!
Yes! Yes!
My friends, there's no reason
to give up on your youth!
This Jutsu...
In the end, only Lee
could make it his own.
Yahoo!
— Hey, Lee...
— I did it! I will do it!
— Lee!
— When I try! I try!
Hey, Lee!
Hey!
Listen to this passionate message
from your teacher!
Oh... what is it?!
Please tell me using hip words.
This Jutsu, the "Lotus"...
it will be dealt with henceforth
as a forbidden Jutsu.
— What?!
— Huh?!
W-What do you mean?
This Jutsu poses a great burden
on the cells of the muscles,
it's a kind of "Self-sacrificing Technique."
Humans normally utilize,
at most, 20 percent...
of the "power" that the muscles have.
Do you understand?
Only 20 percent!
And if nearly 100 percent
of the "power" is used
the muscles themselves will disintegrate.
So, the brain usually controls the "power."
However, this Jutsu forces the
brain's limiter to go off by using Chakra,
allowing high speed continuous Taijutsu...
In other words, this is a dangerous Jutsu
which relies on a secret technique
that brings forth "power" almost
to the limit of one's body.
So the only time it is all right
to use this Jutsu
is when a certain condition is met...
So... when is that?
Are you ready?
Take this to heart...
The condition is...
Guy-sensei...
I will utilize that Jutsu without reserve.
Because this is the time you said..
"When protecting a precious person!"
He disappeared?!
It's just the beginning.
Oh, oh no!
There's no way he can break his fall!
Take this!
Primary Lotus!
This feeling...
Well well...
Just in time.
T-That's impossible!
That is a frightening Jutsu...
It did this much even though
I fell on the spongy dirt.
It's now my turn.
Oh no! With what I just did...
my body still isn't...
Lee!
Your Jutsu is indeed fast.
But our Jutsu exceeds that
and is the speed of sound!
I'll show you there are walls
which effort alone can
never break through.
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
I'm so frustrated!
I'm just pulling feet again.
I'm always just being protected.
I always just watch them from behind.
This time, I need to protect everyone!
Naruto, Sasuke-kun, Lee-san!
I want to be like you too!
Next episode:
"Sakura Blooms! The Back of Determination."
Please watch my battle...